A Guide to the John A. Hartford Foundation records, Grants, Series 8 FA1416
Rockefeller Archive Center
- The American Geriatrics Society (AGS), Enhancing Geriatric Care Through Practicing Physicians Through Continuing Medical Education, Patricia P. Barry (96197-G), 1996-1999 (Box 615, Folder 4527)
- Council on Social Work Education, Preparing Gerontology Competent Social Workers/Strengthening Aging and Gerontology Education for Social Workers (SAGE-SW), Joan Levy Zlotnik (98822-G), 1998-2001 (Box 615, Folder 4528-4530)
- Council on Social Work Education, Preparing Gerontology Competent Social Workers/Strengthening Aging and Gerontology Education for Social Workers (SAGE-SW), Joan Levy Zlotnik (98822-G), 1997-2001 (Box 616, Folder 4531-4535)
- Council on Social Work Education, Preparing Gerontology Competent Social Workers/Strengthening Aging and Gerontology Education for Social Workers (SAGE-SW), Advisory Panel Meeting, Joan Levy Zlotnik (98822-G), 1998-1999 (Box 617, Folder 4536)
- Dartmouth Medical School, Systematic Study of Nature, Extent, Causes and Cost Implications of Small Area Variations, John Wennberg (85163-3H), 1985-1987, 1990-1991 (Box 617, Folder 4537-4539)
- Dartmouth Medical School, Systematic Study of Nature, Extent, Causes and Cost Implications of Small Area Variations, Appendix, John Wennberg (85163-3H), 1986 (Box 617, Folder 4540)
- Dartmouth Medical School, Systematic Study of Nature, Extent, Causes and Cost Implications of Small Area Variations, Reports, John Wennberg (85163-3H), 1981-1982 (Box 617, Folder 4541)
- Dartmouth Medical School, Systematic Study of Nature, Extent, Causes and Cost Implications of Small Area Variations, Reports, John Wennberg (85163-3H), 1981-1982 (Box 618, Folder 4542)
- Dartmouth Medical School, Systematic Study of Nature, Extent, Causes and Cost Implications of Small Area Variations, Articles, John Wennberg (85163-3H), 1975, 1982 (Box 618, Folder 4543)
- Dartmouth Medical School, Replication of Community Centers of Excellence in Aging, John Wasson (96242-G), 1996-2000 (Box 618, Folder 4544-4545)
- Dartmouth Medical School, Replication of Community Centers of Excellence in Aging, Final Progress Report, John Wasson (96242-G), 1998-1999 (Box 618, Folder 4546-4547)
- Dartmouth Medical College, Academic Geriatric Leadership Program: Planning Phase, Paul Batalden (990552), 1999-2001 (Box 619, Frame 4548-4550)
- Dartmouth Medical College, Academic Geriatric Leadership Program: Planning Phase, Report, Paul Batalden (990552), 1999-2000 (Box 619, Folder 4551)
- Grantmakers in Health, Support for "Issue Dialogue" on Heath Professions Education, Lauren LeRoy (2001-0112), 2001-2003 (Box 619, Folder 4552-4553)
- Harvard Medical School, Interdisciplinary Team Training on Geriatric Primary Care, Sue Levkoff (95204-G), 1994-1997 (Box 620, Folder 4554-4555)
- Harvard Medical School, Interdisciplinary Team Training on Geriatric Primary Care, Site Visit and Evaluation, Sue Levkoff (95204-G), 1994, 1997 (Box 620, Folder 4556)
- Harvard Medical School, Center of Excellence, Lewis A. Lipsitz (97200-G), 1997-2001 (Box 620, Folder 4557-4558)
- Harvard Medical School, Center of Excellence, Site Visit, Lewis A. Lipsitz (97200-G), 1997 (Box 620, Folder 4559)
- Museum of Science, Traveling Exhibition on Aging, Steven L. Solomon (98168), 1998-2001 (Box 621, Folder 4560)
- National Chronic Care Consortium (NCCC), Capacity Building in Geriatric Chronic Care, Richard Bringewatt (93334-G), 1993-1996 (Box 621, Folder 4561-4563)
- National Chronic Care Consortium (NCCC), Capacity Building in Geriatric Chronic Care, Interim Progress Report, Richard Bringewatt (93334-G), 1994 (Box 621, Folder 4564-4565)
- National Chronic Care Consortium (NCCC), Capacity Building in Geriatric Chronic Care, Progress Report, Richard Bringewatt (93334-G), 1994-1995 (Box 622, Folder 4566)
- National Chronic Care Consortium (NCCC), Capacity Building in Geriatric Chronic Care, Evaluation, Richard Bringewatt (93334-G), 1994-1995 (Box 622, Folder 4567)
- National Chronic Care Consortium (NCCC), Capacity Building in Geriatric Chronic Care, Geriatrics Scholars Program, Richard Bringewatt (93334-G), 1996 (Box 622, Folder 4568)
- Seattle Institute/VA Medical Center, Client Outcomes in Community Residential Settings in the State of Washington, Susan C. Hedrick (96314-G), 1997-2003 (Box 622, Folder 4569-4571)
- Seattle Institute/VA Medical Center, Client Outcomes in Community Residential Settings in the State of Washington, Miscellaneous Overflow, Susan C. Hedrick (96314-G), 1998 (Box 623, Folder 4572-4575)
- South Carolina Department of Health & Environmental Control, Rural Geriatrics Initiative (RGI), Thomas E. Brown, Jr. (93137-G), 1993-1998, 2003 (Box 623, Folder 4576)
- South Carolina Department of Health & Environmental Control, Rural Geriatrics Initiative (RGI), Thomas E. Brown, Jr. (93137-G), 1993-1998, 2003 (Box 624, Folder 4577-4578)
- South Carolina Department of Health & Environmental Control, Rural Geriatrics Initiative (RGI), Final Progress Report, Thomas E. Brown, Jr. (93137-G), 1996-1998 (Box 624, Folder 4579)
- American Federation for Aging Research, Inc. (AFAR), Medical Student Geriatric Scholars Program, Odette van der Willik (95316-G), 1995-2001 (Box 624, Folder 4580-4582)
- American Federation for Aging Research, Inc. (AFAR), Medical Student Geriatric Scholars Program, Odette van der Willik (95316-G), 1995-2001 (Box 625, Folder 4583-4585)
- American Federation for Aging Research, Inc. (AFAR), Medical Student Geriatric Scholars Program, Students' Research Reports, Odette van der Willik (95316-G), 1996-1998 (Box 625, Folder 4586)
- American Federation for Aging Research, Inc. (AFAR), Medical Student Geriatric Scholars Program, Program Committee Meeting, Odette van der Willik (95316-G), 1998 (Box 625, Folder 4587)
- American Federation for Aging Research, Inc. (AFAR), Medical Student Geriatric Scholars Program, Reports,Odette van der Willik (95316-G), 1995, 1999 (Box 625, Folder 4588)
- American Federation for Aging Research, Inc. (AFAR), Medical Student Geriatric Scholars Program, Reports, Odette van der Willik (95316-G), 1995, 1999 (Box 626, Folder 4589)
- American Federation for Aging Research, Inc. (AFAR), Medical Student Geriatric Scholars Program, Progress Report, Odette van der Willik (95316-G), 2000 (Box 626, Folder 4590)
- American Federation for Aging Research, Inc. (AFAR), Medical Student Geriatric Scholars Program, Interim Progress Report, Odette van der Willik (98310-G), 1999-2000 (Box 626, Folder 4591)
- American Federation for Aging Research, Inc. (AFAR), Medical Student Geriatric Scholars Program, Abstracts, Odette van der Willik (98310-G), 2000 (Box 626, Folder 4592-4593)
- American Federation for Aging Research, Inc. (AFAR), Communications and Dissemination Initiative, Stephanie Lederman (990252), 1998-2003 (Box 626, Folder 4594-4595)
- American Federation for Aging Research, Inc. (AFAR), Communications and Dissemination Initiative, Stephanie Lederman (990252), 1998-2003 (Box 627, Folder 4596)
- American Federation for Aging Research, Inc. (AFAR), Fellowship Cohort Expansion, Stephanie Lederman (2000050), 2000-2003 (Box 627, Folder 4597)
- American Federation for Aging Research, Inc. (AFAR), Centers of Excellence, Approaches to Recruiting and Medical Students and Residents to Careers in Geriatric Medicine, 2004-2008 (Box 627, Folder 4598)
- Huntington Memorial Hospital, Physician Partnership Project, W. June Simmons (91219-G), 1990-1997 (Box 627, Folder 4599-4601)
- Huntington Memorial Hospital, Physician Partnership Project, W. June Simmons (91219-G), 1990-1997 (Box 628, Folder 4602-4604)
- Huntington Memorial Hospital, Physician Partnership Project, Manual, W. June Simmons (91219-G), 1994-1995 (Box 628, Folder 4605)
- Huntington Memorial Hospital, Physician Partnership Project, Publications, W. June Simmons (91219-G), 1992-1995 (Box 628, Folder 4606)
- Huntington Memorial Hospital, Physician Partnership Project, Progress Report, W. June Simmons (91219-G), 1994-1995 (Box 628, Folder 4608)
- Huntington Memorial Hospital, Physician Partnership Project, Miscellaneous, W. June Simmons (91219-G), 1991-1993 (Box 628, Folder 4608)
- Institute for Clinical Evaluation, A Credential in Home Health, J. J. Norcini (990338), 1999-2002 (Box 629, Folder 4609-4610)
- Johns Hopkins University, Strengthening Training in Geriatrics for Physicians, Center of Excellence Program, John R. Burton (97214-G), 1997-2000 (Box 629, Folder 4611-4612)
- Johns Hopkins University, Strengthening Training in Geriatrics for Physicians, Center of Excellence Program, Staff Evaluations, John R. Burton (97214-G), 1994, 1998-1999 (Box 629, Folder 4613)
- Stanford University, Geriatrics Educational Resources and Dissemination Center, Kelley Skeff (94331-G), 1994-1999 (Box 629, Folder 4614)
- Stanford University, Geriatrics Educational Resources and Dissemination Center, Kelley Skeff (94331-G), 1994-1999 (Box 630, Folder 4615-4618)
- Stanford University, Geriatrics Educational Resources and Dissemination Center, Progress Report, Kelley Skeff (94331-G), 1995-1996 (Box 630, Folder 4619)
- Stanford University, Geriatrics Educational Resources and Dissemination Center, Evaluation, Kelley Skeff (94331-G), 1994-1997 (Box 630, Folder 4620)
- Stanford University, Geriatrics Educational Resources and Dissemination Center, Miscellaneous, Kelley Skeff (94331-G), 1995-1997, 1999 (Box 631, Folder 4621)
- Stanford University, Geriatrics Educational Resources and Dissemination Center, Society of General Internal Medicine, Kelley Skeff (94331-G), 1996 (Box 631, Folder 4622)
- Stanford University, Geriatrics Educational Resources and Dissemination Center, Meeting, Kelley Skeff (94331-G), 1996 (Box 631, Folder 4623)
- Stanford University, Enhancing Dissemination of Innovations in Geriatric Education, Georgette Stratos (96236-G), 1996-2000 (Box 631, Folder 4624-4627)
- Stanford University, Enhancing Dissemination of Innovations in Geriatric Education, Evaluation Site Visit, Georgette Stratos (96236-G), 1996-1999 (Box 632, Folder 4628-4630)
- Stanford University Medical Center, Center of Excellence, Peter Pompei (97290-G), 1997-2000 (Box 632, Folder 4631)
- University of California, Los Angeles, Advanced Training in Geriatric Research, Center of Excellence, David Reuben (97201-G), 1997-2000 (Box 632, Folder 4632-4633)
- University of Colorado Health Services Center, Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT) Project, Dennis W. Jahingen (95215-G), 1995-1998 (Box 633, Folder 4634)
- University of Colorado Health Services Center, Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT) Project, Site Visit, Dennis W. Jahingen (95215-G), 1996-1997 (Box 633, Folder 4635-4636)
- University of Colorado Health Services Center, Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Nora Morgenstern, E. K. Burrell (96200-G), 1996-2001 (Box 633, Folder 4637-4639)
- University of Colorado Health Services Center, Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Site Visit, Nora Morgenstern, E. K. Burrell (96200-G), 1997 (Box 633, Folder 4640)
- University of Colorado Health Services Center, Center of Excellence, Andrew M. Kramer (97274-G), 1997-2002 (Box 634, Folder 4641-4643)
- University of Colorado Health Services Center, Center of Excellence, Staff Evaluation, Andrew M. Kramer (97274-G), 1998-1999 (Box 634, Folder 4644)
- University of Connecticut, Centers of Excellence Designation Awards, Richard W. Besdine (97260-G), 1997, 1999-2000 (Box 634, Folder 4645)
- University of Connecticut, Geriatrics in Primary Care Training Initiative, Proposal, Richard W. Besdine (94156-G), 1994 (Box 634, Folder 4646-4647)
- University of Connecticut, Geriatrics in Primary Care Training Initiative, Miscellaneous, Richard W. Besdine (94156-G), 1994, 1998 (Box 635, Folder 4648)
- University of Connecticut, Geriatrics in Primary Care Training Initiative, Proposal, Richard W. Besdine (94156-G), 1994, 1996-1997 (Box 635, Folder 4649)
- University of Hawaii, Center of Excellence, Patricia L. Blanchette (97271-G), 1997-2001 (Box 635, Folder 4650-4652)
- University Hospitals Health System, Improving Geriatric Care Through Learning Teams, M. Orry Jacobs (95227-G), 1994-1997 (Box 635, Folder 4653-4654)
- University Hospitals Health System, Improving Geriatric Care Through Learning Teams, M. Orry Jacobs (95227-G), 1994-1997 (Box 636, Folder 4655)
- University Hospitals Health System, Improving Geriatric Care Through Learning Teams, Progress Report, M. Orry Jacobs (95227-G), 1996 (Box 636, Folder 4656)
- University Hospitals Health System, Great Lakes Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Shirley M. Moore (96307-G), 1996-2001 (Box 636, Folder 4657)
- University Hospitals of Cleveland, 1995 (Box 636, Folder 4658)
- University Hospitals Health System/Henry Ford Health System, Great Lakes Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Nancy A. Whitelaw (96209-G), 1996-2001 (Box 636, Folder 4659-4660)
- University Hospitals Health System/Henry Ford Health System, Great Lakes Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Proposal Exhibits, Nancy A. Whitelaw & Shirley M. Moore (96209-G & 96307-G), 1996 (Box 636, Folder 4662)
- University Hospitals Health System/Henry Ford Health System, Great Lakes Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Proposal Exhibits, Nancy A. Whitelaw & Shirley M. Moore (96209-G & 96307-G), 1996 (Box 637, Folder 4663)
- University Hospitals Health System/Henry Ford Health System, Great Lakes Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Progress Report, Nancy A. Whitelaw (96209-G), 1997 (Box 637, Folder 4664)
- University Hospitals Health System/Henry Ford Health System, Great Lakes Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Evaluation, Nancy A. Whitelaw (96209-G), 1993-1996 (Box 637, Folder 4665)
- University Hospitals Health System/Henry Ford Health System, Great Lakes Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Site Visit, Nancy A. Whitelaw (96209-G), 1997-1998 (Box 637, Folder 4666-4667)
- University Hospitals Health System/Henry Ford Health System, Great Lakes Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Teaching Programs, Nancy A. Whitelaw (96209-G), 1995 (Box 637, Folder 4668)
- University Hospitals Health System/Henry Ford Health System, Great Lakes Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Proposal, Nancy A. Whitelaw (96209-G), 1995 (Box 637, Folder 4669)
- University Hospitals Health System/Henry Ford Health System, Great Lakes Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Nancy A. Whitelaw (96209-G), 1994-1998 (Box 637, Folder 4670)
- University Hospitals Health System/Henry Ford Health System, Great Lakes Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Nancy A. Whitelaw (96209-G), 1994-1998 (Box 638, Folder 4671)
- Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Bay Area Consortium, 2000 (Box 638, Folder 4672)
- Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Bay Area Consortium, Implementation Proposal, Barrie Robinson & Andrew Scharlach (HG003), 1999 (Box 638, Folder 4673)
- Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Bay Area Consortium, Student Training Manual: State of California Aging and Adult Services, 1999 (Box 638, Folder 4674)
- Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Bay Area Consortium, Student Training Manual: San Mateo County Department of Aging and Adult Services, 2000 (Box 638, Folder 4675)
- Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Bay Area Consortium, Consortium Agency Materials, 1999 (Box 638, Folder 4676)
- Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT) Program, On Lok Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT), Interdisciplinary and Discipline-Specific Curricula, 1997 (Box 638, Folder 4677)
- Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT) Program, Rush Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT) Program, Faculty Orientation Information, 1997 (Box 638, Folder 4678)
- Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT) Program, Overheads, 1998 (Box 638, Folder 4679)
- Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT) Program, Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Managed Care Training of Trainers Program, 1998 (Box 639, Folder 4680-4681)
- Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT) Program, Sharing the Care, An Innovative Geriatric Team Model, 1998 (Box 639, Folder 4682)
- Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT) Program, National Programs, 1997-1999 (Box 639, Folder 4683-4684)
- Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT) Program, Preceptor's Manual, 1999 (Box 639, Folder 4685)
- Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT) Program, Seminar Series, Readings and Handouts, 1999 (Box 639, Folder 4686)
- Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT) Program, Seminar Series, Readings and Handouts, 1999 (Box 640, Folder 4687)
- Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT) Program, Video Tape Scoring and Coding Manual, 1999 (Box 640, Folder 4688)
- Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT) Program, Written Case Studies Coding and Scoring Manual (Box 640, Folder 4689-4690)
- Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT) Program, Final Data Presentation, 2000 (Box 640, Folder 4691)
- Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT) Program, Implementation Manual, 2000 (Box 640, Folder 4692-4693)
- Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT) Program, Implementation Manual, 2000 (Box 641, Folder 4694)
- Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT) Program, Psychometric and Statistical Analyses of Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT) Core Measures, Notebook 1, 2001 (Box 641, Folder 4695-4696)
- Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT) Program, Psychometric and Statistical Analyses of Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT) Core Measures, Notebook 2, 2001 (Box 641, Folder 4697-4698)
- Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT) Program, Final Report, 2001 (Box 642, Folder 4699-4701)
- Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT) Program, Site Visit, 2004 (Box 642, Folder 4702-4703)
- Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT) Program, A Curriculum from the Huffington Center on Aging (Box 642, Folder 4704)
- Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT) Program, A Curriculum from the Huffington Center on Aging (Box 643, Folder 4705)
- Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT) Program, Interdisciplinary Approaches to the Care of Rural Elders (Box 643, Folder 4706)
- Geriatric Social Work Practicum Development Program, 2003-2004 (Box 643, Folder 4707)
- Geriatric Social Work Practicum Development Program, Boston University School of Medicine, 1999-2000 (Box 643, Folder 4708)
- Geriatric Social Work Practicum Development Program, Bryn Mawr Graduate School of Social Work & Social Research, 1998-1999 (Box 643, Folder 4709)
- Geriatric Social Work Practicum Development Program, Columbia University School of Social Work, 1999 (Box 643, Folder 4710-4711)
- Geriatric Social Work Practicum Development Program, Columbia University, School of Social Work, 1999 (Box 644, Folder 4712)
- Geriatric Social Work Practicum Development Program, University of California San Francisco, 2000, 2002-2004 (Box 644, Folder 4713)
- Geriatric Social Work Practicum Development Program, University of Hawaii, 2002-2004 (Box 644, Folder 4714)
- Geriatric Social Work Practicum Development Program, University of Oklahoma, School of Social Work, 1999-2000 (Box 644, Folder 4715-4716)
- Geriatric Social Work Practicum Development Program, Virginia Commonwealth University, School of Social Work, 1999-2000 (Box 644, Folder 4717-4718)
- Geriatric Social Work Practicum Development Program, Washington University, George Warren Brown School of Social Work, 1998-2000 (Box 645, Folder 4719)
- ABT Associates, Inc., Corporate Capabilities and Key Staff, 2003 (Box 645, Folder 4720)
- American Academy of Nursing, Donna Regenstreif, 2003 (Box 645, Folder 4721)
- American Academy of Nursing, Geriatric Nursing Initiative, 2002, 2004 (Box 645, Folder 4722)
- American Association of Colleges of Nursing, Enhancing Geriatric Nursing Education, 2005 (Box 645, Folder 4723)
- American Association of Colleges of Nursing, Thank You Note (Box 645, Folder 4724)
- American Academy of Nursing (AAN)/Nursing School Investment Program (NSGIP), Geriatric Nursing School Investment Program, 2004 (Box 645, Folder 4725)
- American Society of Clinical Oncology, 2002, 2004-2005 (Box 646, Folder 4726)
- Beth Israel/Harvard University, Hebrew Life (Box 646, Folder 4727)
- Community Health Management Information System (CHMIS), 1992 (Box 646, Folder 4728)
- Community Health Management Information System (CHMIS), Final Report, 1992 (Box 646, Folder 4729)
- Community Health Management Information System (CHMIS), Functional Design Operating Specifications for a Core Clinical Data Set (Box 646, Folder 4730)
- Community Health Management Information System (CHMIS), Functional Specifications, 1991 (Box 646, Folder 4731)
- Community Health Management Information System (CHMIS), General Overview, 1992 (Box 646, Folder 4732)
- Community Health Management Information System (CHMIS), Meeting, 1993-1994 (Box 646, Folder 4733)
- Community Health Management Information System (CHMIS), Meeting, 1993-1994 (Box 647, Folder 4734)
- Community Health Management Information System (CHMIS), Miscellaneous, 1992-1994 (Box 647, Folder 4735-4737)
- Community Health Management Information System (CHMIS), Overview, 1991 (Box 647, Folder 4738)
- Community Health Management Information System (CHMIS), Request for Proposal, 1992 (Box 647, Folder 4739)
- Community Health Management Information System (CHMIS), Version 2.0, 1992 (Box 647, Folder 4740)
- Community Health Management Information System (CHMIS), California, University of California San Francisco, 1993 (Box 648, Folder 4741)
- Community Health Management Information System (CHMIS), Colorado, 1993-1994 (Box 648, Folder 4742)
- Community Health Management Information System (CHMIS), Detriot, 1992-1993 (Box 648, Folder 4743)
- Community Health Management Information System (CHMIS), Hawaii, 1993 (Box 648, Folder 4744)
- Community Health Management Information System (CHMIS), Maryland, 1992-1994 (Box 648, Folder 4745-4746)
- Community Health Management Information System (CHMIS), New Jersey Institute of Technology (NJIT), 1993 (Box 648, Folder 4747)
- Community Health Management Information System (CHMIS), Utah, 1992-1994 (Box 648, Folder 4748)
- Community Health Management Information System (CHMIS), West Virginia, 1993-1994 (Box 648, Folder 4749)
- The Gerontological Society of America (GSA), Annual Meeting, 2004 (Box 649, Folder 4750)
- Johns Hopkins School of Medicine, Center of Excellence, 2005 (Box 649, Folder 4751)
- National Health Policy Forum, Annual Reports, 2004-2005 (Box 649, Folder 4752)
- New York University (NYU), 2002, 2004 (Box 649, Folder 4753)
- PACE (Program of All-inclusive Care for the Elderly), 2000, 2003, 2005 (Box 649, Folder 4754)
- Partners in Care Foundation (PICF) (Box 649, Folder 4755)
- RAND Health, 2004 (Box 649, Folder 4756)
- Society of General Internal Medicine (SGIM), 2003-2004 (Box 649, Folder 4757-4758)
- Society of General Internal Medicine (SGIM), Academic Internal Medicine Week, 2004 (Box 649, Folder 4759)
- Society of Hospital Medicine (SHM), 2003-2005 (Box 649, Folder 4760)
- Society of Hospital Medicine (SHM), 2003-2005 (Box 650, Folder 4761-4762)
- University of California San Francisco, Nursing, 2004-2005 (Box 650, Folder 4763)
- University of Pennsylvania, Center of Excellence (Box 650, Folder 4764)
- University of Washington, IMPACT Project, 2004-2005 (Box 650, Folder 4765)
- Program Planning Memoranda from Prior Years, 1979, 1982-1984 (Box 650, Folder 4766-4767)
- Program Planning Project Review, 1986, 1988 (Box 650, Folder 4768-4769)
- Paul Beeson Physician Faculty Scholars in Aging Research Program, 1994-1995 (Box 651, Folder 4770)